<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kalarm.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KAlarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KAlarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KAlarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KAlarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KAlarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kalarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KAlarm</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKAlarmxx</name>
  <summary>Personal Alarm Scheduler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Programador d'alarma personal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Osobní plánovač alarmů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Persoonlijke alarmplanner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Osobný plánovač alarmov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Personlig alarmschemaläggning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Персональний планувальник нагадувань</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPersonal Alarm Schedulerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KAlarm is a personal alarm message, command and email scheduler</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KAlarm és un programador personal per a alarmes de missatge, ordres i correu electrònic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kalarm is een persoonlijke planner voor herinneringen, commando's en e-mailberichten</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kalarm schemalägger personliga alarmmeddelanden, kommandon och e-post</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KAlarm — інструмент для складання розкладу повідомлень, команд і поштових повідомлень для нагадування.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKAlarm is a personal alarm message, command and email schedulerxx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Display alarms using your own text message, the text generated by a command, or a text or image file.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mostra les alarmes usant el vostre propi missatge de text, el text generat per una ordre, un fitxer de text o imatge</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Te tonen herinneringen met uw eigen tekstberichten, de tekst gegenereerd door een commando of een tekst of afbeeldingsbestand.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visar alarm med dina egna textmeddelanden, text skapad av ett kommando samt en text- eller bildfil.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">показ нагадувань з визначеним вами текстовим повідомленням, текстом, який створюється вказаною вами командою, або файлом зображення;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDisplay alarms using your own text message, the text generated by a command, or a text or image file.xx</li>
      <li>Audible alarm using a sound file</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Alarma audibles usant un fitxer de so</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Hoorbaar alarm met een geluidsbestand</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hörbart alarm genom att använda en ljudfil</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість створення звукових нагадувань на основі файлів звукових даних;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAudible alarm using a sound filexx</li>
      <li>Recurring alarm on an hours/minutes, daily, weekly, monthly or annual basis, or set it to trigger every time you log in.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Alarma repetida en una hora/minut, cada dia, setmanal, mensual o anual, o definir activar-la cada vegada que accediu al sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Een zich herhalend alarm op basis van uren/minuten, dagelijks, wekelijks, maandelijks of jaarlijks of instellen om het af te laten gaan elke keer dat u zich aanmeld.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Upprepade alarm baserat på timmar/minuter, dagar, veckor, månader eller år, samt inställning för att aktivera det vid varje inloggning.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">повторення нагадування із вказаним інтервалом у годинах, хвилинах, щодня, щомісяця, щорічно або можливість налаштовування нагадування, яке буде показано під час реєстрації у системі;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxRecurring alarm on an hours/minutes, daily, weekly, monthly or annual basis, or set it to trigger every time you log in.xx</li>
      <li>Display alarms color and font customization</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mostra les alarmes amb un color i tipus de lletra personalitzats</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kleuren van te tonen herinneringen en keuze uit lettertypen</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inställning av färg och teckensnitt för visade alarm</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість визначення кольору та шрифту тексту нагадування;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDisplay alarms color and font customizationxx</li>
      <li>Support for multiple alarm calendars, which for example enables you to share alarms between a laptop and desktop computer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementa múltiples calendaris d'alarma, amb els quals serà possible compartir les alarmes entre un ordinador portàtil i l'ordinador de sobretaula</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor meerdere alarm-agenda's, die u bijvoorbeeld herinneringen laat delen tussen een laptop en desktopcomputer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för flera alarmkalendrar, som exempelvis gör det möjligt att dela alarm mellan en bärbar dator och en skrivbordsdator.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка роботи з декількома календарями нагадувань, що, наприклад, уможливлює використання єдиного календаря на ноутбуці і робочій станції.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for multiple alarm calendars, which for example enables you to share alarms between a laptop and desktop computer.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.astrojar.org.uk/kalarm/index.html</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kalarm</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/kalarm/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kalarm.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kalarm</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
